<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Unshaken, 2025 on GYC West</title>
    <link>https://gycwest.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Unshaken, 2025 on GYC West</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gycwest.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Handout downloads for GYC West 2025</title>
      <link>https://gycwest.com/handouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gycwest.com/handouts/</guid>
      <description>  Printable documents  2025 bulletin insert - designed to print in full color on 8.5x11 inch paper. 2024 poster - designed to print in full color on 11x17 inch paper. --   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archives</title>
      <link>https://gycwest.com/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gycwest.com/archives/</guid>
      <description>2024 - Turning Hearts GYC West Yearly Main Event  Each year GYC West hosts a young adult retreat to gain strength in the faith, network safely with like-minded believers, and seek a closer communion with our Father. For 2024 the theme is &#34;Turning Hearts.&#34;
Speakers:  Jeff Walper RJ Gamboa Gabriel Arruda Calvin Gardner  Location: Sierra Pines Camp, CA.
Text: &#34;He will also go before Him in the spirit and power of Elijah, &#39;to turn the hearts of the fathers to the children,&#39; and the disobedient to the wisdom of the just, to make ready a people prepared for the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet GYC West</title>
      <link>https://gycwest.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gycwest.com/about/</guid>
      <description>#inspiration_box { background-image: url(&#34;/img/texture-2136831.jpg&#34;); background-position: center; background-size: cover; background-repeat: no-repeat; }   Mission Statement GYC West exists to motivate and empower Seventh-day Adventist youth and young adults to fulfill their role in God’s plan for these last days. Through training in evangelism, leadership, and discipleship, we provide tools for a life of impactful service. Our retreats rejuvenate mind, body, and spirit, encouraging deeper connections with God and His creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteering</title>
      <link>https://gycwest.com/registration/volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gycwest.com/registration/volunteer/</guid>
      <description>body  section:first-of-type::before { background-image: none; } iframe { width: 100%; height: 800px; }   
 -- Loading...   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration Complete</title>
      <link>https://gycwest.com/registration/complete/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gycwest.com/registration/complete/</guid>
      <description>body  section:first-of-type::before { background-image: none; }   Thank you for registering!  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donating</title>
      <link>https://gycwest.com/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gycwest.com/donate/</guid>
      <description>#inspiration_box { background-image: url(&#34;/img/texture-2136831.jpg&#34;); background-position: center; background-size: cover; background-repeat: no-repeat; }   An Explanation GYC West seeks to provide an annual conference featuring high quality messages for young people living in the western portion of our country. We believe in the power of convocation and that when two or more are gathered together in the name of Jesus, He is there in the midst of us. We know the Lord will bless as we seek the unity that Christ wants for His church as exemplified in the Gospel of John chapter 17.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet GYC West</title>
      <link>https://gycwest.com/2016/idcrisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gycwest.com/2016/idcrisis/</guid>
      <description>.written_by { text-align: right; font-style: italic; }   The Modern Day Identity Crisis Who are we? Where do we come from? What does it mean to be a Seventh-day Adventist? These are questions that too many times go unanswered. Many of us young people are leaving the church because we don’t understand at its core what it means to be a Seventh-day Adventist. We want to be part of something that is more than just a list of beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
