<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reflect: The Daily Experience, 2017 on GYC West</title>
    <link>https://gycwest.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reflect: The Daily Experience, 2017 on GYC West</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gycwest.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Archives</title>
      <link>https://gycwest.com/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gycwest.com/archives/</guid>
      <description>2016 — Identity: Who Are We?  Location: Pine Hills Academy in Auburn, CA.
Text: &#34;And do not be conformed to this world, but be transformed by the renewing of your mind, that you may prove what is that good and acceptable and perfect will of God.&#34; — Romans 12:2 (NKJV)
  Media  Printable Flyer AudioVerse Recordings    Additional Reading  The Modern Day Identity Crisis by Joshua Larson     2015 — Saved to Serve  Location: Weimar College in Weimar, CA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handout downloads for GYC West 2017</title>
      <link>https://gycwest.com/handouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gycwest.com/handouts/</guid>
      <description>  Printable Flyers  ...   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet GYC West</title>
      <link>https://gycwest.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gycwest.com/about/</guid>
      <description>#inspiration_box { background-image: url(&#34;/img/texture-2136831.jpg&#34;); background-position: center; background-size: cover; background-repeat: no-repeat; }   Mission Statement GYC West is an organization of Seventh-day Adventist youth and young adults in the western United States. We believe that the Lord is forming His army of workers in these last days and our prayer is that GYC West would be a vessel through which Jesus Christ can reveal His will.
Purpose GYC West seeks to provide an annual conference featuring high quality messages for young people living in the western portion of our country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Register for GYC West 2017</title>
      <link>https://gycwest.com/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gycwest.com/registration/</guid>
      <description>body  section:first-of-type::before { background-image: none; }   Please note the following conditions:
 Registrants age 15 or younger must have a paid chaperon. Children age 9 or younger are free with a paid chaperon.  Earlybird pricing lasts until the first of May!
 Lodging options:
 Camping on Pine Hills Adventist Academy campus. (Free) Local hotels are available within 5-10 minutes of Pine Hills. (Prices vary) A few RV locations are available, no hookups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet GYC West</title>
      <link>https://gycwest.com/2016/idcrisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gycwest.com/2016/idcrisis/</guid>
      <description>.written_by { text-align: right; font-style: italic; }   The Modern Day Identity Crisis Who are we? Where do we come from? What does it mean to be a Seventh-day Adventist? These are questions that too many times go unanswered. Many of us young people are leaving the church because we don’t understand at its core what it means to be a Seventh-day Adventist. We want to be part of something that is more than just a list of beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>